<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <WULA_Attack_Robber_Camp.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->[bandit]-occupied Wula Empire [camp]</li>
    <li>camp->Camp</li>
    <li>camp->Outpost</li>
    <li>camp->Stronghold</li>
    <li>bandit->Bandits</li>
    <li>bandit->Marauders</li>
    <li>bandit->Fugitives</li>
    <li>bandit->Thugs</li>
    <li>bandit->Outlaws</li>
    <li>bandit->Plunderers</li>
    <li>bandit->Robbers</li>
    <li>bandit->Raiders</li>
  </WULA_Attack_Robber_Camp.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Attack_Robber_Camp.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a request to the colony. A group of warriors from [siteFaction_name] have taken control of an abandoned Wula Empire airdrop outpost. Possibly, this outpost did not follow standard decommissioning procedures, leading to its occupation by aliens. Some technological artifacts inside must not fall into alien hands.\n\nThis camp must be eradicated. The Wula Empire technological artifacts within can be recovered or destroyed on-site. The number of personnel on-site cannot be assessed; there may still be some untriggered &lt;color=#AA3020>&lt;i>pop-up mines&lt;/i>&lt;/color>, but no active Wula Empire turrets have been detected.</li>
  </WULA_Attack_Robber_Camp.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Base_Tex_Quest.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Tithe Taxation</li>
  </WULA_Base_Tex_Quest.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Base_Tex_Quest.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->Only death and taxes are inevitable—submitting tithes on time is the glorious duty of a Wula Empire colony.\n\nThe Wula Empire collects tithes every 10 days, deducted from the colony's assets stored with the fleet. You can construct &lt;color=#6BB7B7>&lt;i>Wula Empire Material Transfer Pods&lt;/i>&lt;/color> to transport materials to the fleet in orbit.\n\nThe Wula Empire shows greater favor to colonies that pay taxes diligently—however, delays will cause displeasure each day, and eventually may even be classified as treason!</li>
  </WULA_Base_Tex_Quest.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Boss_Sky_Lock.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Special Mission: Destroy the Psychic Titan</li>
  </WULA_Boss_Sky_Lock.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Boss_Sky_Lock.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a special request to the colony. A Wula Empire war machine deployed on a transport ship—the &lt;color=#AA74E5>&lt;i>Psychic Titan&lt;/i>&lt;/color>—has gone out of control and is attacking indiscriminately. The Planetary Interdiction Agency had to crash the transport ship onto the planet's surface to prevent escalation.\n\nUnfortunately, the &lt;color=#AA74E5>&lt;i>Psychic Titan&lt;/i>&lt;/color> was not harmed by the crash and continues to wreak havoc on the surface. The colony must face this terrifying beast. The Planetary Interdiction Agency provides the following information:\n\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Internal Circuitry&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The PAt-6 "Psychic Titan" is a powerful psychic war machine, but its psychic circuits are engraved in a closed-loop manner, making it immune to external psychic attacks.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Harbinger of Death&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The Psychic Titan's psychic scream can indiscriminately shatter all targets. Do not engage it head-on unless you have sufficient confidence and means to control it.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Chain Sky Locks&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The Psychic Titan will always appear alongside Sky Locks, which are pure psychic constructs that absorb damage dealt to the Titan. The Psychic Titan cannot be harmed until all Sky Locks are destroyed.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Network Control&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The Psychic Titan has taken control of nearby tank clusters that survived the crash, so the crash site likely hosts more than one enemy.\n\nThe Planetary Interdiction Agency promises that once the rampaging &lt;color=#AA74E5>&lt;i>Psychic Titan&lt;/i>&lt;/color> is defeated, they can recover its psychic circuitry core to construct a brand-new Psychic Titan for the colony.</li>
  </WULA_Boss_Sky_Lock.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Boss_Super_Fortress.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Special Mission: Clear the Giant Fortress</li>
  </WULA_Boss_Super_Fortress.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Boss_Super_Fortress.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a special request to the colony. A &lt;color=#C87451>&lt;i>Giant Fortress&lt;/i>&lt;/color> equipped with volcano cannons has been discovered, not under Planetary Interdiction Agency control—likely a rebel base. Your colony must use all means to eliminate it. The Planetary Interdiction Agency provides the following information:\n\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Preemptive Strike&lt;/i>&lt;/color> This fortress has been hit by EMP artillery from the Wula Empire fleet and requires time to restart its defense systems—but based on bombardment effects, this window may not be long.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Inferno Horn&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The fortress contains four volcano cannons. Once restarted, they will deal devastating damage to all attacking forces and should be prioritized.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Fortified Towers&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The fortress is protected by multiple layers of defensive structures. A frontal assault will be time-consuming, and the fortress roof is specially reinforced, comparable to thick rock roofs.\n&lt;color=#9F0400>&lt;i>-Every Bush a Soldier&lt;/i>&lt;/color> The area near the fortress likely harbors other unseen ambushes. Fleet-detected activity signs here do not match visual observations.\n\nThe Planetary Interdiction Agency promises that once the &lt;color=#C87451>&lt;i>Giant Fortress&lt;/i>&lt;/color> is destroyed, they will dispatch the fleet to bombard the remaining facilities and grant the colony permission to apply for volcano cannons.</li>
  </WULA_Boss_Super_Fortress.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Colony_Promotion.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Promotion Mission: Colony Inspection</li>
  </WULA_Colony_Promotion.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Colony_Promotion.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The colony has accepted an inspection mission.\n\nThe central control AI of the Planetary Interdiction Agency has dispatched one of its avatars and a guard team to the colony. The inspection lasts 12 days. She will examine all aspects of the colony's operations, and you must ensure her mood remains above 25%. After completion, she and the guards will depart via shuttle. If all goes well, you will receive a colony promotion opportunity to unlock more licensed technologies.\n\nBeware—nearby hostile factions have learned that a VIP has arrived at the colony. These raiders will attempt to attack and capture this avatar, and you may face numerous assaults!</li>
  </WULA_Colony_Promotion.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Intro_NewColony.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->New Colony</li>
  </WULA_Intro_NewColony.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Intro_NewColony.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->(Kill all those who ask how to upgrade Wula technology without reading the prompts)\n\nThe Wula Empire's advance team has reached the surface. The fleet has sent them their first communication.</li>
  </WULA_Intro_NewColony.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Intro_Spy.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Cover the Imperial Spy</li>
  </WULA_Intro_Spy.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Intro_Spy.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a request to the colony. A Wula Empire spy has been exposed and is being pursued by other factions—the spy is unarmed and carries vital information. The colony must provide cover until the Wula Empire shuttle arrives to extract them. Although no further details were disclosed, she indicated the attacks would not be too intense, as the spy has shaken off most pursuers.</li>
  </WULA_Intro_Spy.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Kill_PIA_Legion_Escort_Traitor.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Special Mission: Kill the Traitorous Broken Claw Guard</li>
  </WULA_Kill_PIA_Legion_Escort_Traitor.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Kill_PIA_Legion_Escort_Traitor.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a special request to the colony, demanding you kill a Broken Claw Guard member who has betrayed the Empire.\n\nThis will not be a simple task,</li>
  </WULA_Kill_PIA_Legion_Escort_Traitor.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Recycle_PIA_Legion_File.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Promotion Mission: Recover Royal Secrets</li>
  </WULA_Recycle_PIA_Legion_File.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Recycle_PIA_Legion_File.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency has sent a special request to the colony. A safe containing royal secrets has been taken by Wula Empire Progressive rebels. The colony must recover it and return it to the Wula Empire fleet. If the safe has been opened, kill everyone present.\n\nThe rebels are likely attempting to open the safe; you need to check the workbench inside their outpost. Approximately &lt;color=#AA3020>&lt;i>10–20 rebel synths&lt;/i>&lt;/color> have been sighted, along with &lt;color=#AA3020>&lt;i>several active turrets&lt;/i>&lt;/color>.\n\nYou have only 5 days to complete this mission. Once the safe is obtained, you can construct &lt;color=#6BB7B7>&lt;i>Wula Empire Material Transfer Pods&lt;/i>&lt;/color> to send the safe to the fleet in orbit.</li>
  </WULA_Recycle_PIA_Legion_File.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>

  <WULA_Vacation_Quest.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questName->Special Mission: Vacation</li>
  </WULA_Vacation_Quest.questNameRules.rulesStrings>
  <WULA_Vacation_Quest.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
    <li>questDescription->The central control AI of the Planetary Interdiction Agency has grown bored on the fleet and wants to stroll around for a while.\n\nUnless you become hostile to the Wula Empire Planetary Interdiction Agency, it seems your superior plans to stay indefinitely at the colony. You may delete this quest to free up space in the quest list.</li>
  </WULA_Vacation_Quest.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings>
</LanguageData>
