<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.title>Origin: Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.titleShort>Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Kroup star region. This region is a battleground of constant conflict. Due to its position on the fringes and its complex geopolitics, the Wula Empire has never truly controlled it—but the excellent rare crystals and alien natural gas found here are too valuable for the Empire to abandon.\n\nSynths produced here use far more strategic materials than those from other regions. This grants them higher durability, lower energy consumption, and some built-in combat and crafting aptitude.</WULA_Child_Backstory01.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>Origin: Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here use strategic materials far above other sectors, granting them higher body durability, lower energy consumption, and built-in combat abilities.</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.title>Origin: Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.titleShort>Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Daedalus star region. This region is a factory domain near the rim, where countless high-quality alloys are produced to supply the Wula fleets—the beating heart of the industrial districts.\n\nSynths produced here are fitted with powerful production systems, offsetting this model's natural disadvantages in mining and construction.</WULA_Child_Backstory02.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>Origin: Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>Synthetics from here are equipped with powerful production systems, allowing them to offset the natural disadvantages of this type of synthetic in mining and construction.</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.title>Origin: Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.titleShort>Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Palace District. The Palace District is the core of Wula politics and power. Things produced here are generally reserved for the royal family and do not flow to other regions—though there are exceptions.\n\nSynths from here are usually more refined and graceful than those from elsewhere, giving them natural advantages in social and artistic skills.</WULA_Child_Backstory03.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>Origin: Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are usually more refined and elegant than those from other sectors, giving them innate advantages in social and artistic skills.</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.title>Origin: Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.titleShort>Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Delta star region. Delta is a true fortress region. Countless assembly plants spit sulfur and flame, and war machines are the only product here. The moment they step off the line, they join the flood of \"Legion\" and march to the Wula Empire's battlefields.\n\nSynths produced here are designed as dedicated war machines—simple and easy to maintain, with unquestionable combat capability, but not very good at other work.</WULA_Child_Backstory04.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>Origin: Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are designed as dedicated war machines, simple and easy to maintain, possessing undisputed combat capabilities, but not very good at other tasks.</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.title>Origin: Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.titleShort>Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Serris star region. Serris is the Wula Empire's research center. Although the Empire's baseline technology has effectively stagnated, ambitious citizens still flock to its endless stores of knowledge. However, synths produced here are often drafted into local secret projects and rarely get the chance to transfer to other regions.\n\nSynths produced here are research-specialized models. They excel at research, and are among the few synths that can directly control mechanoids—though Wula mechanoids are autonomous machines.</WULA_Child_Backstory05.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>Origin: Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are research-specialized models; they excel at research and are among the few synthetics capable of directly controlling mechanoids—though the Empire's mechanoids are autonomous machines.</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.title>Origin: Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.titleShort>Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Marek star region. Marek is a vast agricultural region compared to others. Multiple planets with excellent astronomical positions are suited for agriculture, allowing it to continuously supply the Wula Empire with huge amounts of food.\n\nSynths produced here usually have built-in housekeeping and agricultural systems, making them adept at everyday chores. Their durable design also causes them to wear down much more slowly under natural conditions than synths from other regions.</WULA_Child_Backstory06.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>Origin: Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced in this star region usually have built-in housekeeping and agricultural systems, making them very adept at handling chores. Additionally, their durable design causes them to wear rate slower than synthetics from other sectors under natural conditions.</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.title>Origin: Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.titleShort>Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synth produced in the Dyson star region. Dyson hosts a vast concentration of astronomical-scale megastructures, a direct testament to the Wula Empire's former might. Naturally, so many giant structures require large numbers of highly adaptable synths to maintain them.\n\nSynths born here have powerful crafting systems. Their nano-repair is designed for self-sustaining repair in extreme environments, so repair consumption is lower than for synths from other regions.</WULA_Child_Backstory07.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>Origin: Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>Synthetics born here possess powerful crafting systems; their nano-repair is designed for self-sustaining repair in extreme environments, thus repair consumption is lower than synthetics from other sectors.</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.title>Origin: Unknown</WULA_Child_Backstory99.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.titleShort>Unknown origin</WULA_Child_Backstory99.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s origin cannot be traced. Perhaps it's a high-quality counterfeit from some region, or a chassis illegally refurbished after salvage. In any case, the serial number on their body is either forged—or simply absent.\n\nThese feral mechanical Wulas can do a bit of everything, but they don't particularly excel at anything.</WULA_Child_Backstory99.description>
</LanguageData>