<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Wula_Synth.label>Synth</Wula_Synth.label>
  <Wula_Synth.description>Synths of the Wula Empire, possessing some characteristics of mechanoids—they are difficult to ignite, immune to common diseases, can self-repair using a nano-system, but require energy to sustain operation.\n\nThey are creations designed by the Wula Empire Royal Mechanist Guild, meticulously replicating the appearance and behavior of their creators. From the birth of the first Wula synth, they have been granted equal human rights—they are not tools, but honorable citizens of the Wula Empire.</Wula_Synth.description>

  <WULA_NanoRepairHediff.label>Nano Repair</WULA_NanoRepairHediff.label>
  <WULA_NanoRepairHediff.description>Wula Empire mechanoids are integrated with a nano-repair system. As long as they have power, they can continuously repair damage sustained by the mechanoid—the system is designed to activate only after a period without taking damage.\n\nThe Wula Empire's highly developed microscopic bionic technology has successfully made this powerful system commonplace. It can be adapted to almost any Wula Empire mechanoid, even repairing external damage on synths, with extremely low consumption, making the Empire's mechanical forces extraordinarily resilient.</WULA_NanoRepairHediff.description>
  <WULA_NanoRepairHediff.stages.0.label>Active</WULA_NanoRepairHediff.stages.0.label>
  <WULA_NanoRepairHediff.stages.1.label>Dormant</WULA_NanoRepairHediff.stages.1.label>

  <WULA_ChargingHediff.label>Energy Overcharge</WULA_ChargingHediff.label>
  <WULA_ChargingHediff.description>The Wula is continuously absorbing energy from the power core.</WULA_ChargingHediff.description>
  <WULA_ChargingHediff.stages.0.label>Charging</WULA_ChargingHediff.stages.0.label>

  <WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.label>Maintenance</WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.label>
  <WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.description>This Wula Empire synth has been active in the harsh rimworld for some time. Although in overall good condition, it has developed minor flaws.</WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.description>
  <WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.stages.0.label>Minor Damage</WULA_Maintenance_MinorBreakdown.stages.0.label>

  <WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.label>Maintenance</WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.label>
  <WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.description>This Wula Empire synth has gone a while without maintenance and is operating with considerable difficulty.</WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.description>
  <WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.stages.0.label>Damage</WULA_Maintenance_MajorBreakdown.stages.0.label>

  <WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.label>Maintenance</WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.label>
  <WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.description>This Wula Empire synth is almost inoperative and requires immediate maintenance, or it will become a pile of scrap.</WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.description>
  <WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.stages.0.label>Critical Failure</WULA_Maintenance_CriticalFailuren.stages.0.label>

  <WULA_Shutdown.label>Shutdown</WULA_Shutdown.label>
  <WULA_Shutdown.description>The mechanical Wula's body energy is completely depleted. All non-core functions are offline, requiring immediate energy replenishment.\n\nIf you need to restart the mechanical Wula, you must build a repair point or synth charging station. A colonist capable of performing medical tasks will bring the incapacitated mechanical Wula to the repair station and use a Wula Empire power core to restart it.</WULA_Shutdown.description>
  <WULA_Shutdown.stages.0.label>Shutdown</WULA_Shutdown.stages.0.label>

  <WULA_MechCarrierSwitchHediff.label>Production Suppression</WULA_MechCarrierSwitchHediff.label>
  <WULA_MechCarrierSwitchHediff.description>This unit's automatic production function has been suppressed.</WULA_MechCarrierSwitchHediff.description>

  <WULA_RemoveSwitchHediff.label>Restart Production</WULA_RemoveSwitchHediff.label>
  <WULA_RemoveSwitchHediff.description>Restart automatic mechanoid production.</WULA_RemoveSwitchHediff.description>

  <WULA_GiveSwitchHediff.label>Stop Production</WULA_GiveSwitchHediff.label>
  <WULA_GiveSwitchHediff.description>Stop automatic mechanoid production.</WULA_GiveSwitchHediff.description>

  <Mech_WULA_Cat_Cute.label>Wula Cat Nearby</Mech_WULA_Cat_Cute.label>
  <Mech_WULA_Cat_Cute.description>A Wula cat that everyone loves is nearby, its adorable appearance attracting colonists' attention.</Mech_WULA_Cat_Cute.description>

  <Wula_Holographic_Flag_Hediff.label>Fighting Under the Banner</Wula_Holographic_Flag_Hediff.label>
  <Wula_Holographic_Flag_Hediff.description>The Emperor watches over me!</Wula_Holographic_Flag_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Cat_Invisibility.label>Special Ops Cat</WULA_Cat_Invisibility.label>
  <WULA_Cat_Invisibility.description>This Wula cat has been specially modified and is invisible to the naked eye, only briefly appearing when firing.</WULA_Cat_Invisibility.description>

  <!-- Screenshot Hediffs -->
  <WULA_Heavy_Infantry_PowerArmor_Mortar_Hediff.label>ILm-60 "Chrome" Mortar</WULA_Heavy_Infantry_PowerArmor_Mortar_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Heavy_Infantry_PowerArmor_Mortar_Hediff.description>A twin-linked light mortar system externally mounted as a backpack weapon attachment on the Wula Empire heavy infantry armor. It can analyze enemy movement and fire autonomously—as long as the wearer is not in melee combat.</WULA_Heavy_Infantry_PowerArmor_Mortar_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>Origin: Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here use strategic materials far above other sectors, granting them higher body durability, lower energy consumption, and built-in combat abilities.</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>Origin: Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>Synthetics from here are equipped with powerful production systems, allowing them to offset the natural disadvantages of this type of synthetic in mining and construction.</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>Origin: Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are usually more refined and elegant than those from other sectors, giving them innate advantages in social and artistic skills.</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>Origin: Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are designed as dedicated war machines, simple and easy to maintain, possessing undisputed combat capabilities, but not very good at other tasks.</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>Origin: Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are research-specialized models; they excel at research and are among the few synthetics capable of directly controlling mechanoids—though the Empire's mechanoids are autonomous machines.</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>Origin: Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced in this star region usually have built-in housekeeping and agricultural systems, making them very adept at handling chores. Additionally, their durable design causes them to wear rate slower than synthetics from other sectors under natural conditions.</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>Origin: Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>Synthetics born here possess powerful crafting systems; their nano-repair is designed for self-sustaining repair in extreme environments, thus repair consumption is lower than synthetics from other sectors.</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_Beam_Weapon_Aiming_Hediff.label>Beam Preheat</WULA_Beam_Weapon_Aiming_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Beam_Weapon_Aiming_Hediff.description>Before firing, Wula Empire beam weapons need to preheat for a period, after which they can fire continuously.</WULA_Beam_Weapon_Aiming_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_RW_Base_Loitering_Munition_Hediff.label>Loitering Munition Guidance System</WULA_RW_Base_Loitering_Munition_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_RW_Base_Loitering_Munition_Hediff.description>The guidance system of the WLl-35 "Zeolite" allows its loitering munition to be fire-and-forget, but it can only be active for a short time.</WULA_RW_Base_Loitering_Munition_Hediff.description>
  <WULA_RW_Handle_Cannon_Burn_Hediff.label>Armor Melt</WULA_RW_Handle_Cannon_Burn_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_RW_Handle_Cannon_Burn_Hediff.description>The large beam weapons of the Wula Empire will melt enemy armor, reducing their resistance to heat.</WULA_RW_Handle_Cannon_Burn_Hediff.description>
</LanguageData>
