<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Childhood Backstories -->
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.title>Origin: Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.titleShort>Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Kroup star sector. This sector is a war-torn land—due to its remote location and complex geopolitics, the Wula Empire has never truly controlled this sector, but its excellent rare crystals and alien natural gas make the Empire unwilling to relinquish control.\n\nSynthetics produced here use strategic materials far above other sectors, granting them higher机体耐久, lower energy consumption, and内置了一定的 combat and crafting abilities.</WULA_Child_Backstory01.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>Origin: Kroup</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here use strategic materials far above other sectors, granting them higher机体耐久, lower energy consumption, and内置了一定的 combat abilities.</WULA_Child_Backstory01_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.title>Origin: Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.titleShort>Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Daedalus star sector. This sector is a factory星域 near the frontier worlds, where countless high-quality alloys for the Wula fleets are born, the搏动的心脏 of the industrial zones.\n\nSynthetics from here are equipped with powerful production systems, allowing them to抵消此型合成人在采矿和建造上的天然劣势.</WULA_Child_Backstory02.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>Origin: Daedalus</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>Synthetics from here are equipped with powerful production systems, allowing them to抵消此型合成人在采矿和建造上的天然劣势.</WULA_Child_Backstory02_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.title>Origin: Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.titleShort>Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Palace District. The Palace District is the core of Wula Empire politics and power; things produced here are typically皇室专供 and not外流 to other sectors—though there are exceptions.\n\nSynthetics produced here are usually more refined and风度翩翩 than those from other sectors, giving them innate advantages in社交和艺术.</WULA_Child_Backstory03.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>Origin: Palace District</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are usually more refined and风度翩翩 than those from other sectors, giving them innate advantages in社交和艺术.</WULA_Child_Backstory03_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.title>Origin: Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.titleShort>Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Delta star sector. The Delta sector is a true fortress sector, where countless assembly factories迸溅着 sulfur and flame; war machines are the sole product—they join the "Legion's"洪流 upon leaving the production line,奔赴 the Empire's battlefields.\n\nSynthetics produced here are designed as专用战争机械, simple and easy to maintain, possessing无可争议的战斗能力, but不太擅长 other tasks.</WULA_Child_Backstory04.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>Origin: Delta</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are designed as专用战争机械, simple and easy to maintain, possessing无可争议的战斗能力, but不太擅长 other tasks.</WULA_Child_Backstory04_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.title>Origin: Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.titleShort>Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Serris star sector. The Serris sector is the Wula Empire's科研中心; though the Empire's basic technology has factually stagnated, aspiring individuals within the Empire still趋之若鹜 to the sector's endless knowledge stores. However, synthetics produced here are often抽调去 local秘密项目, rarely having opportunities to be transferred to other sectors.\n\nSynthetics produced here are科研特化型号; they excel at research and are among the few synthetics capable of directly操纵机械族—though the Empire's mechanoids are autonomous machines.</WULA_Child_Backstory05.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>Origin: Serris</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced here are科研特化型号; they excel at research and are among the few synthetics capable of directly操纵机械族—though the Empire's mechanoids are autonomous machines.</WULA_Child_Backstory05_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.title>Origin: Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.titleShort>Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Marek star sector. The Marek sector is a vast农业型星区 compared to others. Here, multiple planets with得天独厚的天文位置 are suitable for agricultural production, enabling it to源源不断地输送大量食材 to the Wula Empire.\n\nSynthetics produced in this星域通常内置了家政和农业系统, making them very adept at handling杂事. Additionally, their durable design causes them to磨损速度 slower than synthetics from other sectors under natural conditions.</WULA_Child_Backstory06.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>Origin: Marek</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>Synthetics produced in this星域通常内置了家政和农业系统, making them very adept at handling杂事. Additionally, their durable design causes them to磨损速度 slower than synthetics from other sectors under natural conditions.</WULA_Child_Backstory06_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.title>Origin: Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.titleShort>Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a synthetic produced in the Dyson star sector. The Dyson sector集中建立了 numerous天文级别的巨型空间结构, a direct体现 of the昔日 Wula Empire's雄厚国力. Such massive structures naturally require many高适应性的 synthetics for maintenance.\n\nSynthetics born here possess powerful手工系统; their nano-repair is designed for自持修复 in extreme environments, thus repair消耗 is lower than synthetics from other sectors.</WULA_Child_Backstory07.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>Origin: Dyson</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.label>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>Synthetics born here possess powerful手工系统; their nano-repair is designed for自持修复 in extreme environments, thus repair消耗 is lower than synthetics from other sectors.</WULA_Child_Backstory07_Hediff.description>

  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.title>Origin: Unknown</WULA_Child_Backstory99.title>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.titleShort>Unknown Origin</WULA_Child_Backstory99.titleShort>
  <WULA_Child_Backstory99.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s origin cannot be traced—perhaps a high-quality imitation from some sector, or a机体 illegally reprocessed after回收; in short, the机体编号 on their body is either forged or simply absent.\n\nThese wild mechanical Wulas know a bit of everything but excel at nothing特别.</WULA_Child_Backstory99.description>
</LanguageData>
