<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <WULA_BrokenPersonalityTrait.degreeDatas.0.label>Mechanical Wula</WULA_BrokenPersonalityTrait.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_BrokenPersonalityTrait.degreeDatas.0.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a Mechanical Wula. Wulas think differently from ordinary people; under extreme stress, their simulated personality will completely collapse.</WULA_BrokenPersonalityTrait.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_WhitePaper.degreeDatas.0.label>Blank Slate</WULA_Trait_WhitePaper.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_WhitePaper.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s memory banks are mostly empty. [PAWN_pronoun] can learn quickly and shape [PAWN_possessive]self.</WULA_Trait_WhitePaper.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Knight.degreeDatas.0.label>Imperial Knight</WULA_Trait_Knight.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Knight.degreeDatas.0.description>My body belongs beneath the Emperor's sword,\nMy name is blessed by the Emperor,\nI travel through the boundless sea of stars,\nAnd I swear by my soul to the Emperor:\n\nAlways treat the Empire's people with kindness; always show compassion to the helpless and the weak.\nAlways show mercy to innocent women and children; always regard all living beings as equals.\n\nAlways purge the Empire's traitors in the name of valor; always slay the Empire's enemies in the name of a knight.\nAlways raze rebel cities in the name of the Empire; always cleanse the endless cosmos in the name of the Emperor.\n\nAlways contemplate the Empire's troubles with wisdom; always answer ignorant doubts with patience.\nAlways discern life's truths with devotion; always guide billions of citizens with faith.\n\nAlways explore the Empire's domains with the will to discover; always seek the unknown with the will to learn.\nAlways follow the Emperor's footsteps with tenacity; always scrutinize the truths of the star-sea with a seeking heart.\n\nI am the Emperor's shield, and I am the Emperor's sword.\nIn the name of the Wula Emperor, I am an Imperial Knight!</WULA_Trait_Knight.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Legal_Officer.degreeDatas.0.label>Legal Officer</WULA_Trait_Legal_Officer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Legal_Officer.degreeDatas.0.description>Legal officers are frontline enforcers of the Wula Empire's knight orders. They are well trained in shooting, and they have the smooth tongue needed to suppress and placate slaves.</WULA_Trait_Legal_Officer.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Sculptor.degreeDatas.0.label>Sculptor</WULA_Trait_Sculptor.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Sculptor.degreeDatas.0.description>Sculptors are scientists at the Wula Empire Observatory. They treat gene editing as the ultimate artistic medium, and living organisms as raw materials—creating one-of-a-kind \"living artworks\" with striking aesthetic value or philosophical meaning.</WULA_Trait_Sculptor.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Diplomat.degreeDatas.0.label>Diplomat</WULA_Trait_Diplomat.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Diplomat.degreeDatas.0.description>Wula Empire diplomats are known as Heralds. Even their polished etiquette can't hide the arrogance and condescension of a fallen empire.</WULA_Trait_Diplomat.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Nun.degreeDatas.0.label>Nun</WULA_Trait_Nun.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Nun.degreeDatas.0.description>Wula Empire nuns are the backbone of the Grand Cathedral. They cast aside the pampered life of a fallen empire and carry out preaching crusades in person to uphold their devout faith.</WULA_Trait_Nun.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Researcher.degreeDatas.0.label>Archivist</WULA_Trait_Researcher.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Researcher.degreeDatas.0.description>To uncover and preserve the Wula Empire's lost knowledge, the archivists of the Imperial Library tirelessly wade through an ocean of books.</WULA_Trait_Researcher.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Connector.degreeDatas.0.label>High-dimensional linker</WULA_Trait_Connector.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Connector.degreeDatas.0.description>After maintaining a cross-dimensional link with an extraplanar installation for so long, these Wulas have gradually become less human.</WULA_Trait_Connector.degreeDatas.0.description>

  <WULA_Trait_Broken_Personality.degreeDatas.0.label>Shattered Personality</WULA_Trait_Broken_Personality.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <WULA_Trait_Broken_Personality.degreeDatas.0.description>This Wula Empire synth lacks a complete personality, making them more like a true machine.</WULA_Trait_Broken_Personality.degreeDatas.0.description>
</LanguageData>
